you
next
time.
See you
next
time.
What is this?
A map of the world.
What about it?
Nothing. It's...
it's shaped like a lady. Alright.
Let's go, hero.
An audience with the king, huh?
I'm gonna screw this up for sure.
Oh, you don't have to
worry about any of that.
Just be yourself.
After all, we consider you to be
a treasure created by our goddess.
So in that sense,
you're actually the only one here
who is considered equal to royalty.
Wait, what does that mean?
The goddess of love and beauty
created our kingdom's royal family.
The first king received her blessing,
and now her crest only appears upon the
bodies of those who
inherit that same blessing.
It proves that they are of the
goddess's family, so to speak. I see.
So that's why it could
be considered perjury.
Hasn't it occurred to you that
Tachibana's crest might be fake?
You seem surprisingly prepared.
You arrived too quickly
after we caused the uproar,
and there's no delay in getting
an audience with the king.
Hey, Shen, how long have you
had your sneaky eyes on us?
Oh dear, have I been found out?
What is with you, dude?!
Begging your pardon, Supervisor, but
haven't you introduced yourself yet?
What do you mean?
Sorry, I should have said.
You see, I've been entrusted with the
intelligence operations of the whole kingdom.
My name is Muriya.
I will be more than
happy to attend to your
needs during your stay
in our lovely little...
Oh, and to think that all this time
you've actually been the heroes, Jinguji.
No wonder you're so strong.
I do hope that you'll continue
to favor me with your patronage.
I can prove useful, I swear,
particularly in the bedroom at night.
Honored heroes, follow me.
The king awaits.
I appreciate you coming.
We welcome you!
Most honored heroes summoned
here to us by our divine goddess!
I can't.
I want to go home now.
No, don't freak out.
All I see is an old guy
you'd find at any sauna.
The characters in Isekais always
make this stuff look so easy.
How do you get through an audience
with royalty without popping a vessel?
We are pleased to have the
opportunity to meet you, Your Majesty.
Tachibana.
Uh-huh, I see.
He intends for me to charm the king to
give us an edge in the discussion, huh?
Take this!
This is my smile, the
cutest in all of history!
Hiya, your majesty!
Uh, was the double P sign too much?
Our goddess's creations are indeed sublime
and lovely, just as one would expect.
And it didn't even work?
I'm ready to die now.
The goddess's creations?
Is that from the prophecy too?
Is it really possible that the heroes are
unaware of the contents of the prophecy?
Correct.
Well, if that's the case,
bring out the liar, please.
I'll stop the war with the war
Everyone is shukki shukki by chuu
By our Goddess's hand,
a beautiful young woman was created
and summoned here as our true hero.
Find the ones bearing the Holy Crest
so that we may be led to safety,
that is what her words
must mean. Well done.
You managed to turn it
into something nice.
Heroes who have been summoned here
by the Goddess of Love and Beauty,
you must do whatever it takes
to defeat the Demon Lord!
Demonstrate our Goddess's might
by being the first to find him!
We are with you!
We won't hesitate to lend you
our support! Really? Support?
What kind, specifically?
Well, let's see.
Surely we could give them our national
budget for the year, couldn't we?
Will the national budget be enough?
Fine!
The military budget, too!
Let's give them the taxes!
Well, at least we know my
charm definitely worked.
So it looks like my cuteness
does prove pretty useful, huh?
And I think it's about time you
finally acknowledged it, don't you?
Do it.
I won't deny that it's a
handy face to have around,
but it just doesn't do it for me.
Seriously?
So after all I've done to help,
you're still anti-my cuteness?
You know, ever since I became like this,
you've been a lot colder towards me.
Like, remember when you
were fighting with Shen?
Please excuse me for interrupting.
Tell me right now, do you like Shen's
body more than mine, yes or no?
Just a misunderstanding.
Need something?
Oh, yes, of course.
I almost forgot to tell you, we've
just decided to hold a banquet tonight.
What kind of banquet?
Well, at least they wear normal
clothes at a time like this.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
So what do you think?
The maids really went for it, and
I think it was worth it, don't you?
Aw, check it out.
You changed, too.
Looking snazzy, sir.
Ahhhhhhh! Shin! Smelling salts! Now! Yep!
Uh, what's wrong?
Sorry, you're banned. Why?
This sucks so hard.
It's just ridiculous, I wanna go inside!
There's nothing to be done though.
Ugh, come on!
Will this be enough?
Uh, thank you!
Wow!
Any alcohol?
Yeah, but not for you.
What would you do if it turned
out like that other time?
Don't be such a stick-in-the-mud, man.
Just a sip.
I think not.
The drinks are pretty strong.
You jerk.
You mean you've already had some?
No fear.
Oh, it'd be tough to be you, Tachibana.
Because I must say, the liquor in
this kingdom is truly delicious!
You didn't need to say that.
Is it good?
I wanna drink good liquor!
I wanna drink it!
Give it to me!
Tachibana, that's enough.
Hey, what the heck is with you?
Lately, you've been far too
careless, and that's not okay.
Stop assuming that you'll
be fine if it's just me.
What do you think's gonna happen if I stop
being able to fight off your charm here,
huh?
It's a celebration.
There's really no need for you
to get as worked up as all this.
No, this is good.
Can you even imagine the
state I was in earlier?
This is a teaching moment,
because it's hell on earth.
Your conduct has been intolerable.
Are you listening?
Hey, Tachibana!
Are you disheartened?
Why, do I look disheartened?
You were all ragey in her face.
Anyone would react like that.
Where does he get off
scolding me when he's the
one who's got to come to
terms with the way I look?
Wait.
Maybe I should leave him alone.
I know what that look on his face meant.
Though it's been a while
since I've seen it.
It's a warning.
Jinguuji was seriously cautioning
me in his own way, but I...
I just...
I'm still me!
I gotta fight to say who I am!
This curse is making me crazy!
Jinguji's not what I want!
I am a 32-year-old man, and my ideal
is a young, beautiful, blonde woman!
Kind of innocent, if
possible, but still sharp!
That's very important,
and kind of melancholy!
Yeah, just...
like that.
Is anybody there?
What the heck possessed
me to run and hide?
Goodbye, world.
What are you doing?!
I mean, it's pretty obvious
I was about to jump, right?
Uh-huh, uh-huh, hence the freakout!
Are you trying to convince me not to?
Well, yeah, you know, like you do,
suicide is not good for your health!
Shut your mouth, it's pointless!
Everything in this world is pointless!
Well, what about, I mean...
Why?
Why is this happening?
What are we supposed to
do in this situation?
I've heard things like don't
give up have the opposite effect.
Should I try to distract her or something?
Hey, could I bother you
for a little bit of advice?
Advice?
You weren't born here in
this country, were you?
You can tell.
You're so beautiful.
I've never met anyone who looks like you.
I think you're much more
beautiful than I am.
Why am I hitting on her? Right.
I'm safe. I'm a girl. It's fine.
I'm tired of those.
The words of praise.
Okie dokie.
So,
the person I'm traveling with,
we've actually been together
ever since we were little.
He can kinda do anything.
But now I'm afraid I'm
becoming a burden to him.
So I tried to see if there was anything
I could do to make it easier on him,
but I couldn't come up
with a single thing.
And I really thought that
at a banquet of all things
I might be able to use my
looks to help out somehow.
But I not only failed at that
I got him mad at me again!
Interesting I understand that completely.
You were trying to make
that person think you
were cute but you failed
and now you're depressed.
That's not it the gentleman
you like can't seem to
see you such a common
problem really that's not it?
I'm so sorry, but I've
never not been admired,
so I have a feeling I'm not the best
person to offer you advice on this.
Aha.
Listening is not in her skill set.
You know,
I was only looking for
some general advice or
ideas of how not to cause
my partner more work, so...
So after all I've done to help,
you're still anti my cuteness?
Did I...
want him to praise me?
Oh man, I can't deny it.
I totally love basking in
that feeling of superiority.
But if all I wanted was
to feel cute and superior
I could just charm some
other man It's just being
flattered by other guys
doesn't really do anything for
me why wow you're amazing
I'm proud of you I mean have
I ever once been praised
by him in all the years
we've known each other oh
god I haven't like never do
I obsessively need him to
be impressed with me So
I'm roughly as mature as
your standard eight-year-old?
It's clear that you must love
that person very much indeed.
No, wrong.
You're a truly hopeless case.
Has anyone told you
you're deeply unhelpful?
At least it did prove to
be a nice distraction.
Bye, thank you.
I really like you a lot, you know.
My feeling this way about
Jinguji is the curse's fault.
I know that for a fact.
I mean, it's obvious,
considering just spending
time with that beautiful
girl has made me feel like
I'm on top of the world.
This is who I really am.
Those other feelings are fake.
Seriously, though.
She smells so good!
Breathing down my neck as usual.
I want more than anything
to see your smile.
What's that?
What's wrong with you?
I just really hope you two will
make up as quickly as possible.
Hey, Tatsubana?
Bye, thank you.
I really like you a lot.
Who are you?
Huh?
Did I summon you?
The hero is you!
I had no idea! Princess!
Wait, princess?
Welcome.
I am the first princess of this
kingdom and I'm called Yigrain.
Last night I didn't know who you were
and I was terribly impolite. I see.
So she's the reason
Tachibana's acting so strange.
Honored hero, I've come before
you today with a request.
Would you please take me with you on your
great journey to defeat the Demon Lord?
It feels like destiny!
Oh, hero, allow me to accompany you!
Please, I'm begging you!
No, of course you can't.
Our journey here is difficult,
dirty, and dangerous.
Call it the three Ds.
Far from the kind of carefree
fantasy a child might imagine.
Ah, there it is.
Condescension.
What a shock.
Would you please kindly stay
out of this conversation?
I happen to be addressing our
honored hero right at the moment.
Really?
You know what you should do?
You should try going out
and having a little fun.
You're obviously serious and intelligent.
But you don't know much
about the world, do you?
Truth be told, you have every appearance
of a stiff and pointless kind of man.
It's always just been the same.
Prideful men are all like this.
Jinguuji, what are you doing?!
I know you're angry, but Arson
is not the answer, buddy!
Please, let's think about this!
Oh,
this is like when a supervisor
once asked for a party-level
trick performance and Jinguuji
made the fire alarm go off,
which then resulted in party
tricks being declared forbidden
on the spot all because of
his ultra-special technique,
fire breathing!
So tell me, was that entertaining
enough for you, princess?
Wow, this guy.
I assume you meant it as revenge
for my treating you like a child,
but I fear you've picked
the wrong opponent.
Unfortunately, there
is nothing I cannot do.
Why do you want to travel
with us in the first place?
It's not.
That's enough, isn't it, Jinguji?
She's hesitating because she's got
a reason not to tell us, right?
Pushing it would be childish.
Oh, my hero.
Tachibana.
I'm really sorry, dude, but logic and
reasoning is not gonna work on a kid like her.
It's too much of a risk.
Goodbye, world.
The thought of accidentally
pushing her over
the edge literally scares
the crap out of me.
We gotta try some other tactic.
Something gentler.
Oh, of course you can't go! No!
Suddenly you must go on a journey?
What about your official duties then?
And besides all that, siding against
the demon lord will be dangerous.
That's right.
When dealing with stubborn kids, sometimes
it's best to turn to their parent.
Think about it,
you can't even get dressed
by yourself and you can't
get to sleep without
holding your favorite doll.
I wasn't expecting a public execution.
Impressive as usual, Tachibana.
Leaving this to her
father means her heart is
guaranteed to be smoothly
and efficiently crushed.
I was right in thinking you're
suited to human resources.
I wish you'd punch me
for foolishly believing
you wanted to bring a
woman on our journey.
What do you think, honored hero?
As things stand...
It is just as you say, Your Majesty.
At the least, she should be able to
go to the bathroom alone at night.
And as royalty...
Why are you making it worse?
Don't panic, Tachibana. It's all right.
I know what's up here.
Break her until there's
nothing left, right?
He doesn't know what's up at all!
Biggie, you understand, don't you?
You mustn't ask for things like
a willful child might anymore.
Oh, father.
It slipped.
And Four Eyes, are you
having fun looking so smug?
Even though you don't
understand a single thing?
This is ridiculous, everyone's stupid!
Hey, Moji, guess what?
I don't care about demon
lords or heroes anymore!
This Moji never will ever get the dog!
Wait, so she knew?
Your Majesty, please stay strong!
Princess?
Wait, Tachibana.
We may be inside the castle, but
you can't go off on your own.
You better not follow me.
You are the worst at
dealing with teenagers.
I need to do this alone.
Princess, are you there?
What the what?
What are you doing?
Well, obviously, I'm venting my anger.
I can see that.
I have to do at least
this much or else, see?
This is what it means to live here.
That's awesome!
It's great you have a healthy
way to blow off steam.
But considering that, why
don't we try to calm down?
Well, Hero, the truth is, I don't even
have the freedom to leave if I wanted to.
You have to understand, my
mother died when I was born.
So my father became
overly protective of me.
I don't have any friends close
to my age who share my station.
No memories of running
across grassy fields.
Nothing.
I've never found anything
I really wanted to do.
It all feels so pointless.
Okay.
I've seen this before.
No wonder I can't leave her alone.
Princess.
Is there anything that I can do for you?
I'll help out.
If you have something in your
head that you've been dreaming of?
Then I want to make it a reality!
Do you mean that?
You really are going to help me?
Yeah, of course
Rise, my people! Yeah!
A king has caught up an outward beauty
and forgets true Earth's adventure rule!
Hold up, princess? What are we doing?
The leaders of the rebellion are
Princess Ygrane and the hero.
The rebel army is calling for a new ruler
and the abolishment of
hereditary succession.
How did this nightmare happen?
It's too late.
We have no choice.
We'll deploy the military and...
If we do that and Iggy
gets hurt, then what?
We can't!
It's impossible!
Well then,
what if we use the Intelligence Department
to contain the Princess in secret?
Would that work?
That's good.
You got it?
Intelligence Department!
Isn't this the right time for a
deadweight department to shine?
Can you do it?
Yeah, of course we can!
I just want to say good luck,
and we're all counting on you.
So, the highlight was our Supervisor,
who couldn't seem to refuse,
is now orchestrating a last-ditch
attack on the Rebel Army.
I see.
I guess that's good.
Even when melancholy or sublime.
Tachibana, what should I do?
Staying with a rebel
army is too dangerous.
I want to drag you back here
even if it's against your will.
Yay!
You better not follow me.
Could it be that Tachibana actually
wanted to travel with that woman?
That can't be it, right?
No.
It's possible.
She's just the type Tachibana
usually likes, plus she's a princess.
When we went to have the
king give her a scolding,
was it actually to have the
king give his permission?
Even though you don't
understand a single thing?
Wait, I don't understand a single thing?
Tachibana, I don't get it, what
the heck am I supposed to do?
Hmm?
I shall give my report.
I'm afraid that Mouria has
failed and been captured.
So futile after all.
Somehow, I had a feeling it would be...
What a coincidence. So did I.
No other choice.
Call in that person!
What person?
Oh
Yeah
Reincarnated as a fantasy
knockout and a rebel army.